http://www.brianregan.com/privacy-policy

Tour
Specials & series
Store
Privacy Policy
Musictoday has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Musictoday and all other web sites powered by Musictoday.Privacy Statement for MusicToday
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. Musictoday uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart in the stores and to keep track of your membership status on the Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. The cookies we use only track your currently logged in status or your shopping cart status. Our registration form requires users to give us contact information (name and e-mail address) and demographic information (zip code). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and about companies we choose. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and may be shared with other select companies who want to contact the user. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We do not share mailing address, credit card, or any personally identifiable information (other than e-mail address) with other companies. Demographic and profile data are used only for personalized Web content and statistical information and are not shared with other companies except in ways that do not personally identify our users.This site contains links to other sites. Musictoday is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We place advertising on our site that originates from third party advertisers and/or advertising agencies. Even though these advertisements are embedded in our Web site, cookies may be assigned by the advertisers themselves. Musictoday does not control those cookies.Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (e-mail address) and financial information (credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send our customers' orders and information about our company and about companies we choose. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and may be shared with other select companies who want to contact the user. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial and contact information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services and may be shared with companies that help us operate our site, such as the credit card companies that we use.Musictoday runs contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (e-mail address) and demographic information (zip code). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and about companies we choose. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and may be shared with other select companies who want to contact the user. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We may share your contact and demographic information with the contest prize providers.Musictoday provides online ticketing to venues and artists in which we ask customers for contact information (e-mail address and mailing and billing addresses). Musictoday provides your contact information to the venues, artists and/or promoters of the events for which you purchase tickets. By purchasing tickets, you acknowledge that Musictoday has no control over and is not responsible for the privacy policies of those venues, artists or promoters or their subsequent use of your contact information.In addition, Musictoday collects and stores statistics and other information about the online activities of our users on an aggregated (collected) basis. For example, we track the number of people who view each page, the order in which pages are viewed, and other information to learn which features are the most popular and to refine our design and marketing efforts.You agree that Musictoday may assign, sell, license or otherwise transfer to a third party your personal information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of all or substantially all of the assets or capital stock of Musictoday, inc. or its affiliated entities.Public ForumsSecurityChildren's GuidelinesChoice/Opt-OutCorrect/UpdateContacting the Web SitePublic ForumsThis site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.SecurityThis site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our database servers are protected from intruders by a Cisco firewall router and your credit card transactions are enacted using 128-bit SSL encryption. We may be required to release personal information about you as a result of a lawsuit or subpoena or as immediately necessary to protect our rights or the rights and safety of others. Additionally, "perfect security" does not exist on the internet.Children's GuidelinesMusictoday strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children's online activities and to consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personally identifiable information without parental permission. Although the Musictoday site is not directed to children under the age of 13, Musictoday doesNOT collect online contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.NOT entice children under the age of 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.Choice/Opt-OutOur site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.This site gives users the option of removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.You can send e-mail to unsubscribe@musictoday.com or visit http://musictoday.com/edit_member.aspCorrect/UpdateThis site gives users the option of changing and modifying information previously provided. Email correction@musictoday.com or visit http://musictoday.com/edit_member.aspContacting the Web SiteIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:Privacy Policy AdministratorMusictodayP.O. Box 1911Charlottesville, VA 22903privacypolicy@musictoday.com
